Junior Web Developer with experience working as part of an agile scrum team utilizing JavaScript, React Redux to create components and pages for large e-commerce Knowledgeable platform. and passionate about the development complete lifecycle including functional and automated testing. Excellent project manager with the ability to contribute to a design team from point-of-conception to release.



TECHNICAL SKILLS

- JavaScript
- Redux.js
- CSS3
- Node.js
- Jest.is
- WDIO
- GitHub
- JQuery Materialize
- APIs
- AJAX
- Handlebars.js
- MongoDB

- React.is
- HTML5
- LESS.js
- Express.js
- enzvme
- cucumber
- Media Queries
- Bootstrap
- Firebase
- JSON
- MySQL
- PHP

EDUCATION & TRAINING



Full-stack Coding Certificate University of Minnesota 2018





Event Management Int. College of Management, Sydney

ABROAD

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Junior Front End Engineer

Best Buy via Brooksource

- August 2018-Present Support the front-end capabilities of the e-commerce platform as
- part of the post-purchase attach team Provide support in software development lifecycle from concept and design to testing and deployment
- Create new pages and components that encompass business, design, accessibility and analytics requirements using JavaScript, React, Redux and other technologies
- Assist with improvement of on-boarding process and implementation of new department-wide knowledge base

Freelance Web Developer

Dani Carter Codes

May 2018-Present

- Created a multi-page custom website for a local startup, rabbitGrub: Vegan Food Bike Cart using JavaScript, Node.js, Express.js, Caleander.js to show upcoming events, GoogleMaps API to show the current location and PubNub API to track the bike.
- Used Wordpress CMS to update to update Creo Kids Academys website branding using custom CSS.
- Developing a web store application for a local charter school using JavaScript, Node.js and Express.js that utilizes Nunjucks templating engine and MongoDB as the database.

Activities and Co-Curricular Coordinator

Osseo Area Schools

November 2017-August 2018

- · Event management from conception to completion including event scope, vendor-relations, marketing/brand consistency, budgeting on-site management and evaluation
- Key project objectives include ensuring brand consistency, maintaining budget and meeting stakeholder standards

Administrative Assistant

Osseo Area Schools

October 2016-November 2017

- · Comprehensive management of front office
- Served as main point-of-contact Delivered assistance to scholars, families, and staff

Banquet Captain

Green Mill Catering

July 2016-April 2017

 Managed execution of off-site events including: ensuring delivery of catered items, schedules, customer service, and kitchen management

Membership Manager

Phi Sigma Sigma Inc.

January 2013 - March 2015 January 2016 - May 2016

Responsible for half of the collegiate and alumnae chapters across North America, with focus on leadership, recruitment, event planning, chapter operations, finances, community service and philanthropy





